（雀の鳴き声）
（男鹿）ぎゃあああ～～！！
（爆発音）
（ベル坊）ヒィ～　ヒィ～。
ガッ　ガガ…。
ダッ　ダダッダッ…。
（ヒルダ）そうですか…→
Is that so?
恐ろしい
カブト虫の夢を　ご覧になり→
You had a scary dream of a rhinoceros beetle,
つい　寝ぼけて
しまわれたのですね。
ダブダーッ！
and are still half asleep, aren't you?
ご安心ください。
もう大丈夫ですよ。坊っちゃま。
Please, rest easy. Everything
will be okay, Master.
全然　大丈夫じゃね～だろ。
Okay my butt!
イッ！？
えっ！？
ダァ～～！！
ああ～～…。
（爆発音）
ほらね～っ！？
See what I mean?!
What Are the 6 Holy Knights?
≪やっだ～　何あれ≫
≪怖いわよね　石矢魔って…≫
Ew... What's with that?
Ishiyama sure is scary...
≪しっ！見ちゃダメよ≫
Shh! Don't look...
≪かんべんしろよな～≫
≪マジ　消えてくれっつの≫
Give us a break...
I wished they'd get lost, seriously.
（邦枝）あっ…。
やっぱ　こいつ誰かに
押し付けないとダメだわ…。
Yeah, definitely gotta
pawn him off onto someone.
（古市）けど　あの東邦神姫ですら
ダメだったんだぞ？
Sure, but even the TKKH couldn't cut it.
この学校にベル坊が懐くほど
強いヤツがいると思うか？
You really think there's someone strong
enough for Baby Beel at this school?
だよな…。
No kidding...
（アレックス）
トップクラスの不良と聞いて
少しは期待してマシタが…。
I had a bit higher expectations for people
from a top-class delinquent school.
（ＭＫ５）ううっ…。
（アレックス）
案外　たいした事ないデスね。
がっかりです。
But you were surprisingly trivial to defeat.
What a disappointment!
≪こいつらは　ザコですよ≫
They're just the small fry.
では　その男鹿君とやらは
期待していいのデスか？
Are you saying I should expect
better from this Oga-kun fellow?
ええ…。自分も
会うのが楽しみですよ。→
Yes... I'm looking forward
to meeting him myself.
なあ　男鹿…。
Isn't that right, Oga?
（チャイム）
Self Study
なんかさ…人数　減ってね？そうか？
Uh, are we missing people?
Really?
見ろよ。ＭＫ５とか
グッドナイトとか居ないだろ。
Look... The MK5 and Good Night aren't here.
サボってんじゃね～の？
（姫川）妙な噂が流れてんだ。
Aren't they just cutting class?
I've heard some odd rumors...
（姫川）この学園の　影の守護神が
動き出した～とかなんとか。
Some so-called shadowy guardians of this
school have started making their move...
影の守護神？
Shadowy guardians?
（邦枝）六騎聖…。
私も聞いたわ。→
The 6 Holy Knights.
I heard the rumor, too...
そいつらが石矢魔の生徒を
追い出そうとしてるって噂。
They're trying to drive out
all the Ishiyama students.
（由加）ん～。でも
この学校に姐さん達より→
Yeah, but I can't imagine this school havin'
anyone stronger than you, Madame Aoi.
強いヤツらがいるなんて
考えられないっスけどね～。
それが　そうでもないらしいよ～。
（由加）マジっスか！？
I wouldn't say that.
Seriously?!
この学校　部活動が盛んだろ？→
The extracurricular activities
thrive at this school, yes?
各競技のエキスパートで　かつ
成績も　超優秀な連中が→
6 people are chosen each year.
Experts in all kinds of physical
competition, with superior grades to match.
毎年６人選ばれて　学校行事や
風紀を取り締まってるんだとさ。
They enforce the traditions and
public morals of the school.
（寧々）もしかしたら　ＭＫ５たちもそいつらに…。
Then, were the MK5 and the
others done in by them?
（神崎）ヘッ。何ビビってやがる。→
What're you so scared of?
そうだとしても　そいつは
ＮＧ５や　グッドモーニングが→
Even if that's true, the MK5 and
Good Morning are just chumps.
ザコだったってだけだろ？
はぁ？
それとも
急に怖くなったのか？
And you're now suddenly afraid?
（寧々）
何　アンタ？
話に入ってくんじゃないわよ。→
What was that? When did I give
you permission to butt in?
それとも構って
ほし～いんですか？あ～ん？
Or are you just begging for
a little attention, huh?
どこ掴んでんだ　バカ女。
誰がバカ女だって？
Hands off me, you stupid bitch.
Who're you callin' a stupid bitch?!
（邦枝）やめなさい！
Enough, you two!
チッ…。
す…すいません。姐さん。
I-I apologize, Madame...
いや…そうか…
やっぱ…だよな…うん。
Hmm, yeah, I guess so...
ん？何ブツブツ言ってんだ？そうか…。
What're you muttering about?
I see...
はぁ？
バカはダメなんだ。
An idiot won't do.
何の話だよ。忘れてんじゃね～ぞ。
What're you talking about?
Forgetting something, are we? I'm talking
about dumping Baby Beel off on someone.
ベル坊を押し付けるヤツを
探すって話だよ。
バカはダメなんだ　バカは！→
Idiots aren't going to cut it!
あいつも　こいつも！
Him! And him!
ああン？
俺？
Me?
そう　ダメ！絶対！
Yeah! Not even close!
す…すいません！
こいつ今　テンパってるもんで！
I'm sorry... He's kind of
like, on edge right now...
…ってなわけで
当面の目的が決まったぜ！
Which means my goal is set!
俺より頭の良い
六騎聖とやらを探す！
I'm gonna find these 6 Holy Knight
people who're smarter than me!
（古市）《俺より頭の良いって
それ　全員だと思うよ…》
Smarter than him?
I think we're all smarter than him...
（校内放送チャイム）
（校内放送：木戸の声）
あ～。石矢魔高校特設クラスの→
Kunieda and Oga from Ishiyama
High's Special Class...
邦枝と男鹿
すぐ　生活指導室に来るように。
Please come immediately
to the Counselor's Office.
あっ？
この声…。
Huh?
That voice...
（木戸）
先日　君たちと約束したはずだ。あ？何だっけ？
If I'm not mistaken, you
promised the other day...
Huh? Promised what again?
ほら　あれよ
石矢魔再生計画。
You know, that... the Ishiyama
Reformation Project.
（木戸）
しかし　相変わらず　君たちは
学園内で騒ぎを起こしてばかり。→
But as usual, all you people do
is cause trouble in the school.
見たまえ　おかげで佐渡原先生は
ノイローゼになってしまった。
Just look at Sadohara-sensei...
He's turned into a basket case.
（佐渡原）わ…私の愛車が…。
ローン１０年分…→
M-My beloved ride... 10-year loan...
壊れた車に１０年分…。
ダーブーッ！
10 years... Car destroyed...
（木戸）それにだ。前から言おうと
思っていたが　その赤ん坊。
And this... I've been wondering
from the start, but that baby...
はっ？
ニョッ？
（木戸）全裸の男の赤ん坊を
これ見よがしに→
Because you've been walking
around with a naked baby,
連れ歩いているせいで　一部の
女生徒が困惑しているそうだ。→
many of the girl students are upset.
せめて　服でも着せたら
どうかね？
Could you at least put some clothes on him?
あ　あの…。お言葉ですが
それは校則に…。
U-Um, if I may, is there some
school rule regarding...?
（木戸）フ…。残念だが　あるんだよ。
Sorry, but there is.
School Rule
You Cannot Be Fully Naked
ああっ…。
まあ　ともかく…
このままだと我々も→
W-Well, anyway...
At this rate we are going to have
to take more extreme measures.
強行手段を
取らざるを得なくなる。
強行手段？
Extreme measures?
この学校にも　腕力で君たちを→
I'm saying there are people in this school
who have the power to completely dominate you.
圧倒できる者たちが居る
ということだよ。
あ～　六騎聖って　ヤツ？
Oh yeah... Those 6 Holy Knight folks?
（木戸）な…なぜ　その名前を！？
H-How do you know that name?
ちょうど　会いたかったんだわ。
そいつら　どこに居んの？
Perfect! I wanted to meet them.
Where are they?
いや　お前　会いたいって…。
Wait... You... want to meet them?
（佐渡原）ひぃぃぃ！！
恐ろしい！六騎聖！
So frightful! The 6 Holy Knights!
六騎聖！六騎聖が来る～！
そして　ローン１０年分が～！
The 6 Holy Knights... The
6 Holy Knights are coming!
Plus, my 10-year loan!!
（木戸）≪佐渡原先生
しっかりして下さい≫
（佐渡原）≪ローンが　ローンが…≫
Sadohara-sensei, please
get a hold of yourself.
まったく　何なのよ
六騎聖って。
Honestly, what's with these
6 Holy Knight people?
和なら　知ってっかな～。はっ？
Maybe Kazu knows?
俺　ちょっと
聞きに行ってみるわ。
I'll go ask him.
（邦枝）ちょ…聞きに行くって！？
ちょっと　待ちなさいよ！？
Go ask him? H-Hey, wait!
（古市）はぁ…。男鹿はクイーンと
呼び出しくらっちまうし→
Oga and the Queen got called out...
教室は息苦しいし　行き場ねぇ…。
I can't stand being in that classroom...
Nowhere for me to go...
（三木）≪古市君≫んっ？
Furuichi-kun.
（三木）久しぶり。
俺のことを覚えてる？
How's it been?
Do you remember me?
お前…三木？
You're... Miki!
（三木）１人かい？男鹿君も
一緒だと思ったんだけど…。
Alone?
I thought Oga-kun would be with you...
お～　三木！
やっぱ　三木か～！久しぶり～。→
Oh, Miki! It's you, Miki!
Long time no see!
そっか　お前
この学校だったんだな！→
I see... So, you went to this high school?
前と雰囲気違うから
最初　わかんなかったよ！→
You seem like a different person,
I didn't recognize you at first.
中学の時以来だもんな～！
Last time we met was in middle school, right?
あっ…。
（三木）君たちは
相変わらずのようだね。
I see that you people haven't changed.
校舎を壊したんだって？
いや　それ…俺じゃないから。
I hear you destroyed the school building?
Yeah, well... That wasn't me.
（古市）
まったく　あいつと居るってだけで俺まで犯人扱いだ。
Man, just being with them gets
me treated like a criminal.
（三木）２人は　いつも
つるんでたもんね。
Well, you two are always together.
（古市）けど　お前…変わったよな。
（三木）そう？
But... You've sure changed.
I have?
（古市）
昔は　もっと　おどおどしてたと
思ったけど…。モテるだろ？
You were a lot more sheepish back
then. I bet you're popular now.
（三木）い～や　全然。
No. Not at all.
またまた～！
モテるって絶対！→
Oh, come on now.
I bet you're a hit with the ladies.
俺にも可愛い子
フフッ…君も紹介してくれよ！相変わらずだね。
Introduce me to some cuties, would ya?
And you haven't changed one bit.
いや～しかし
知ってるヤツが居て助かったよ。→
Well, I'm just glad I know someone here.
正直　この学校
アウェイ感がハンパなくてさ。
Honestly the cold shoulder I'm
getting at this school damn harsh.
不良アレルギーだからね
ウチは。
We're allergic to delinquents.
いや　だから
俺は不良じゃないって。
Yeah, but I'm not a delinquent, see...
アッハハ…そうだね。
でも　忠告しとくよ。→
That's true! But, I'll warn you...
彼らのターゲットは
今　完全に君たちになってる。
Their sights are now firmly set on you people.
はっ？
Huh?
（三木）どっちが強いとか
そういう事じゃないんだ。→
It's not about who's stronger...
戦った時点で君たちの負けだ。
それを教えておきたくてね。
You'll lose the moment you
actually start to fight.
That's what I wanted to tell you.
ちょ…ちょっと待てよ？
急に何なんだよ…彼らって？
H-Hey, what? What're you...
Who do you mean, "they"?
六騎聖…。
The 6 Holy Knights.
彼らとは
絶対に戦っちゃいけない。
You must not fight them, no matter what.
最近　な～んか学校の雰囲気が
重苦しいよね～。
Man, it's so suffocating
in the school recently.
あ～石矢魔の連中が
転校してきたせいでしょう？
Yeah. It's all 'cause that bunch
transferred in from Ishiyama High.
ホント　あいつら
石矢魔じゃなくて石ヤバって感じ。
Seriously, it's more like they're
from Oh, shit!-yama than Ishiyama...
（梓）え～？でも
いい人たちだよ～。
Huh? But they're nice people!
Azusa, don't tell me...
梓　あんた…まさか！？
うん。結構
仲良くなったんだ。
Yup! I'm pretty good friends with them!
えへへ…
一緒にケーキ食べたりとか。あっ。
We went and ate cake together, for example.
あんたね…。いいかげん
警戒心ってものを持たないと→
You seriously need to get
some sense of danger!
そのうち　悲惨な目に遭うわよ。
If you don't, you'll
be on the road to disaster!
（友人）そうよ。男はオオカミ。
特に石ヤバのヤツらは！
That's right! Men are wolves!
Especially the ones from O-shi-yama!
Remember what happened
with the physicals?
こないだの身体測定の時なんか
赤ん坊を連れた石ヤバの男子が→
I heard the guy with the baby peeped
at the girls when they were changing!
女子の着替え覗いてたって
噂もあるんだから！
（梓）あ～　それ　男鹿さんだ～。
Oh, that's Oga-san!
男鹿さん？
それって…→
Oga-san?
Is he the one that has a naked baby on
his back for some reason, like this?
こんな感じに　なぜか
素っ裸の赤ん坊を背負った？
（生徒達）うわぁ～～！！
出たぁ～　石ヤバ～！？
They're here!
O-shi-yama!
（梓）あ～　男鹿さんだ！
Oh, it's Oga-san!
Wazzap!
オッス。
ダッス。
Wazzap.
≪あれが男鹿…≫
≪石ヤバ最強の…≫
The strongest from O-shi-yama...
≪目があったらヤバいぞ≫
Don't make eye-contact.
Kazu around?
和　いる？
He's in the bathroom right now!
今　トイレに行ってます。
長いんで多分…。
He's taking a while, so he's probably...
梓　しゃべっちゃダメ！
Azusa, don't say it!
子供　できるわよ！？
You want to get pregnant?!
Come on... The teachers told
us not to come over here.
ほら…先生に　こっちへは来るなって言われてるでしょう。行くわよ。
Let's go.
あっ　邦枝先輩も
一緒だったんですね。→
You're here too, Kunieda-senpai?
こんにちは～。
デートですか～！？
Hello! On a date?
えっ！？
デ…デデデ…デート！？
D-D-D-Date?!
いやっ　そ…そんな
ここ　学校だし～！！
N-No way! I-I mean, we're at school!
Come on, let's go already!
ほら　早く行こ！
いや　聞きたい事あってさ。
Actually, I wanted to ask him something.
あっ…。
こいつ。
ニョ？
See, this guy...
俺より強くて頭のいいヤツなら
こいつも懐くような気がしてさ→
I have a feeling he'd take a liking to
someone that's stronger and smarter than me.
代わりに　面倒みてもらおうと
思って探してんだわ。
I was hoping they could
look after him instead.
So I'm looking for them.
探すって　誰をです？
六騎聖って連中。
Looking for them? For who?
These 6 Holy Knight people.
え～っ！！
It's all over...
≪終わりだ…≫
≪その名を口にするなんて…≫
Just by saying their name...
He's dead meat!
≪死ぬぞ　あいつら…≫
≪ヤバすぎるって≫
Holy shit, indeed!
（鈴の音）
I do hope you put up more of
a fight than those others.
（アレックス）今度は　ザコじゃないと
いいのデスが。
あ？
（鈴の音）
それって　どういうことだよ？
六騎聖と戦うなって…。
What do you mean by that?
Don't fight with the 6 Holy Knights?
言葉通りの意味さ。
（三木）
男鹿にも伝えておいてくれ。
It means exactly what it
means. Tell Oga for me.
（古市）ちょ…ちょっと待った！→
W-Wait a sec!
だいたい　その六騎聖って
どんなヤツなんだよ？→
Who are these 6 Holy Knight people anyway?
何か特徴とかねえのか？
（三木）…エンブレム。
Do they have some special
feature or something?
The Emblem.
Emblem.
エンブレム？
On the collar of their uniform, they
wear an Emblem in the shape of a lion.
（三木）
彼らはみな　制服の襟に獅子を
かたどったエンブレムをつけている。
って　お前のその校章みたいにか？
（三木）ん？ああ…→
You mean, like that school badge you wear?
Oh, this?
普段は表裏を
ひっくり返しているから→
You might not be able to tell, since
it's usually worn on the underside.
わからないかもしれないけどね。
お…お前！？
とにかく忠告はしたよ。
（三木）
Y-You're...
Anyway, I've warned you.
Hey, Miki!
おい！三木！？
（山村）あ～　すっきりした～！→
Man, what a load off!
やっぱ不良たるもの
学校でうんこしないとな～…ん？
Delinquents like me gotta
take dumps at school, yup!
Perhaps I shall start again
and introduce myself.
改めて
自己紹介シテおきましょうか…。
はじめマシテ。聖・石矢魔部長連合
ボクシング部部長　そして…→
How do you do? I am St. Ishiyama's
Captains' Union Boxing Club Captain,
and one of the 6 Holy Knights,
六騎聖のひとり
新庄アレックスです。
Shinjo Alex.
（鈴の音）
Sakaki-kun,
榊君…君には協調性というものが
ナイのデスカ？→
don't you have any sense of cooperation here?
私ひとり名乗って
バカみたいじゃナイデスか！→
Now I look like an idiot, being
the only one to give his name!
サァ　名乗りなさい
何者だ　君は！
Come on, tell them your name! Who are you?!
Moe.
（榊）
萌え…。
（アレックス）はぁ？何言ってんの君！→
Huh?! What did you just say?!
てゆ～か　目を開けなサイ！→
And open your damn eyes!
ホラ　君のせいで
完全にナメられてるよ！
Thanks to you, they totally
think I'm a weakling!
ど～してくれるんデス
この空気！
You'd better get with the program!
Shijo from the Boxing Club and
Sakaki from the Kendo Club!
（山村）ボクシング部の新庄さんに剣道部の榊さん。
あの２人が六騎聖だって噂は
やっぱり本当だったんだ…。
The rumors that those two were part
of the 6 Holy Knights were true!
あ～？何だ？こいつらが
例の六騎聖ってのか？
ダー？
Huh? What? So you people are
two of the 6 Holy Knights?
油断しないで。
２人とも相当な使い手よ。→
Don't let down your guard.
The both of them are very skilled.
特に　あの長髪…。
Especially the one with the long hair.
Crap... He's not someone you
could easily escape from.
《マズイわね…簡単に
逃げられるような相手じゃない。→
And if we lay hands on them,
the both of us are expelled.
かといって
手を出せば　２人とも退学…》
どうだ　ベル坊。アイツらは？
ダーブー！
How about them, Baby Beel?
Yeah... I guess they have to show you how
strong and smart they are, don't they?
そっか～。やっぱ強くて頭のいい
とこ見せてもらわないとな～。
《ダメ　この人　全然わかってない。私がなんとかしなきゃ…》
No... He doesn't understand at all.
I have to do something.
What do you want? We just came
to see some acquaintances.
何の用かしら？私達
知り合いに会いに来ただけよ。
六騎聖だか　何だか知らないけど→
You might be some 6 Holy Knights or whatever,
無抵抗の人間に
暴力はふるえないでしょ？
but it's not like you'd be violent
with people unprovoked, right?
いいえ　お嬢さん
残念ながら　それは勘違いです。
On the contrary, Miss. I'm
afraid you are mistaken.
我々が行うのは　暴力ではない…
制裁です。
What we are about to do is not violence.
It is sanctioning.
《竹光で…》
With a wooden sword?
Oh? She dodged it?
《ほう…あれを避けますか》
Did something just happen?
今　何かあった？
わ　わかんない…。
く…邦枝先輩…。
I-I can't tell...
K-Kunieda-senpai!
梓ちゃん　定規か何か持ってない？
え？
Azusa-chan, do you have a ruler or something?
Wait, seriously? With that?
おいおい　まさか　あれで？
相手は六騎聖だぞ。
殺されるんじゃねえか？
She's fighting one of the 6 Holy Knights!
She's gonna get killed!
Impossible. The sword strike of
a master is faster than 250 km/h.
《無茶です。達人の初太刀は
時速２５０ｋｍをこえるといいます。→
If you use something like that to parry a blow
剣道部主将　榊君もしかり…→
そんな物で受けて　下手すれば
ケガだけじゃ済みませんよ》
from the kendo captain,
Sakaki, it won't be pretty.
来なさい。
Get on with it.
Incredibly... moe...
激…萌え。
《なんてことはない　この女…
それよりも　さらに速い！》
This woman sure is something...
And so incredibly fast!
わ～　邦枝先輩　すご～い！
You're amazing, Kunieda-senpai!
ダーッ！
I see. Perhaps I underestimated you.
なるほど。少しあなた達を
みくびってマシタよ。
Let's be serious about this.
本気でやりまショウ。
Oh? Finally my turn, huh?
お～　やっと俺の出番か。
（指を鳴らす音）
（アレックス）何をしているのデス。
あ？
What are you doing?
Put down that baby on your back.
（アレックス）
背中の子供を降ろしなサイ。
いくら私が天才でも　その子の
トラウマにならないように→
Even though I am a genius,
it would be difficult for me to defeat
you without traumatizing that baby.
あなたを倒すのは　難しいデスよ？
Don't worry 'bout him.
心配すんな。こいつ　こう見えて
なかなかの根性もんだ。
ダッス！
He might not look it, but he's pretty gutsy.
フッ　それでこそ子連れ番長。
では…→
No wonder they call you the BoB Brawler.
Then I will proceed without hesitation!
遠慮なくいきますヨ？
こっちも遠慮なく
試させてもらうぜ。
Show me everything you've got!
お前が本当に
俺より頭いいかをな。
You'd better prove that
you're smarter than me!
待ちなさい！
戦ったら退学に！
Hold it! If you fight, you'll be expelled!
問題…→
Question...
その１！
...number 1!
A grandma and grandpa are in a certain place!
あるところに　おじいさんと
おばあさんがおりました！
Answer me this: Which one is stronger?
さて　強いのは　どっちでしょ？
It's over.
終わりデス。
（ゴング）
お　男鹿…。
Oga?
≪な　何でクイズ？≫
≪石ヤバのやることは
わかんねえ≫
Why did he quiz him?
I don't get how O-shi-yama does things...
≪ていうか
答えもわかんないけど≫
I don't know the answer, either.
あ…アニキーッ！
Brother!
アニキ　何てことを…。新庄先輩の
一発をモロにくらうなんて→
Brother, what are you doing?
Taking a direct blow from Shinjo-senpai?
How self-destructive could you be?!
自殺行為にも　ほどがある！
Hold it there.
ちょっと待ちなさい！
まだ彼は負けてないわよ。
He hasn't lost yet.
いいえ　もう終わりデスよ
お嬢さん。
No, it's over, Miss.
そ　その通りです…。新庄先輩は
今まで全ての公式試合を→
Definitely...
Shinjo-senpai has ended every boxing
match he's ever had with a one-punch KO.
一発ＫＯで終わらせてるんです。
成績は全国総体で２位→
And he has the second-best
record in the entire country.
I don't care who you are,
if you take a direct hit...
いくらアニキでも
あれをまともにくらっちゃ…。
それでは。
０点だ。
Well then...
0 points.
男鹿！
アニキ！
Oga!
Brother!
（アレックス）今　何と？
What did you just...
俺の問題に即答できねえような
アホは→
Idiots who can't answer my questions
get 0 points, you bastard.
０点だっつってんだ。ドカスが。
ちょっとショックですネ。
I'm somewhat shocked.
安心しろ。もう一度だけ
チャンスをやる。→
Don't worry. I'll give you another chance.
Answer it carefully...
心して答えろよ！
むか～し　むか…。
Once upon a time...
...there was a...
ある…とこ…ろに…。
Oga!
男鹿！
悪い　こいつ　ちょっと頼むわ。
うまくパンチがかわせねえ。
Sorry... Can you hold him a second?
I can't dodge his punches very well.
You think it's the baby's
fault you can't dodge them?
赤ん坊のせいで
かわせなかったとでも？愚かな…。
Fool. It is impossible for an amateur
like you to dodge a boxer's punches.
素人がボクサーのパンチを
かわすなど　不可能デス。
あいつの言う通りよ。
それに　こっちが手を出したら…。
出さねえよ。
He's right!
And besides, if you fight back...
I ain't going to.
それより　絶対に俺から
１５ｍ以上離れるな。
Anyway...
Do not get any farther
than 15 meters from me.
《えっ…》
《離れるな…つまり　そばにいろ。
そばにいてくれ？→
"Don't go away from me?"
In other words... "Stay by my side?"
"Will you stay by my side?"
一生　俺と一緒にいてくれ？
って　ええええ！？→
"Together, forever?" "Be with
me the rest of my life?!"
ウソーッ！
まだ心の準備が～！》
No way! I'm not emotionally prepared for...
らじゃ…。
ダーブッ。
Roger.
Okay, Captain! It's your final chance!
さ～て大将　最後のチャンスだ。
俺をガッカリさせんなよ。
Don't disappoint me now!
それは…こっちの台詞デス！
That's my line!
The final question:
最後の問題です。
パンはパンでも…。
When is a door...
...not a door?
食べられないパンは？
あっ！
ああっ！
フ　フライパン…。
おおっ！！
（ピンポーン！）
W-When it's ajar?
何ぃ！？何で答えが？
お前　天才か！？
What?!
H-How did he know?!
Are you a genius?!
見ろ　ベル坊！
やっぱこいつ　頭いいぞ！
Look, Baby Beel! He really is smart!
割と強え～し
こいつなら文句ねえだろ？
He's pretty strong, too! He
wouldn't be a problem, right?
プー…プー…。
寝てらっしゃる！
He's friggin' asleep!
何故だ！
何が不満だというのだ！？
ちょっと静かにしなさいよ。
Why?! What does he lack?
Hey, keep it down!
せっかく寝たのに
起こしちゃうでしょ！
You're going to wake him after
he finally went to sleep!
（アレックス）
やめデス。興が冷めました。→
I give up. I have lost interest.
これ以上やると
拳を痛めますしね。→
My fists will hurt if I continue on.
And besides, we were just supposed
to test the waters today.
それに
もともと今日は　様子見デス。
Until the next time... With Miki-kun.
いずれまた。
今度は　三木君と一緒に。
三木？
Miki?
男鹿さ～ん！邦枝センパーイ！
無事でよかったっす！
Oga-san! Kunieda-senpai!
I'm so glad you're okay!
どうなることかと思った～。
I didn't know what was gonna
happen for a bit there!
でも　さすがはアニキっす。
例の８００ボルトの超必殺技は→
But you sure were impressive, Brother!
You must have sealed your secret 800 volt
attack because it was too dangerous, right?
危険すぎるんで
封印してたんですよね？
戦いの中でも
相手の事を思いやるなんて→
To sympathize with your opponent like that...
I respect you more and more!
ますますソンケーします！
《あれが六騎聖…普通なら
大会出場停止処分なのに→
Those are the 6 Holy Knights...
Usually they would be suspended from
entering competitions for something like this.
Attacking us out in the open like that?
表立って攻撃してくるなんて…→
I guess they really are
sanctioned by the school...
やっぱり学校側が
認めてるとしか…》
男鹿も気になる？
ああ　やっぱりだな。
Doesn't it worry you too, Oga?
Yeah, it's just as I thought...
Indeed.
（邦枝）だよね。
やっぱり妙に懐いてやがる。
He really does like you.
は？
Come on already, why don't you be his mother?
もうお前が母親でいいんじゃね？
え？は　は…はは！
そんなこと言ってる場合じゃ
ないでしょ～！！
Now is not the time!
Only 3 of the 6 Holy Knights
have shown themselves.
Where are the other 4?
6 minus 3 is 3, damn it!
What's black and white and red all over?
Are you still going on with that?
What can you put on, but never take off?
Demon World Briefs!
What can you only see with your eyes closed?
Hilda-san's swimsuit that I
can only see in my dreams!
On the next Beelzebub:
Who Could the 6 Holy Knights Be?
I will become the Riddle King!
I suck at impressions!